allmusicals.com 2013-04-20

# Lyrics for All Musicals and Broadway Casts

Privacy Policy

Allmusicals.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this web site: Allmusicals.com

Information Automatically Logged  
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site.

Advertisers  
We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.  
Read Amazon [privacy policy here](http://rcm.amazon.com/e/cm/privacy-policy.html?o=1). Read AllPosters [privacy policy here](http://www.allposters.com/help/guarantee.asp#privacy).

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)

External Links  
This site contains links to other sites. HitsLyrics.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. Public Forums   
This site forum and guestbook available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

Security  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.

Fair Use Notice  
This web site may contain copyrighted material whose use has not been   
specifically authorized by the copyright owner. This page is operated under the assumption that this not-for-profit use on the Web constitutes a "fair use" of the copyrighted material as provided for in Title 17, Chapter 1 , section 107 of the US Copyright Law. If you wish to use this copyrighted material for purposes of your own that go beyond "fair use", you must obtain permission from the copyright owner. 

Contacting the Web Site  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us.

©2012 allmusicals.com. Lyrics are property & copyright of their owners & provided for educational purposes only
